afi.com 2001-06-20

# Asian Financial Intelligence

---  
The Internet contains a wealth of information - unfortunately this may include your name, address, phone number or e-mail address. When you are online, sites you visit may collect personal information without your knowledge. At AFI.com, your privacy is of paramount importance to us. We are committed to meeting, and where possible, exceeding, internationally recognized standards of personal date privacy protection, in complying with the requirements of the Hong Kong Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Chapter 486 of the Laws of Hong Kong) (the "Ordinance"). We recognize and appreciate the need to safeguard details of a visitor using our site as a registered user. The following are our views and practices regarding this matter.   
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, please email us at [admin@afi.com](mailto:admin@afi.com).   
AFI.com will at all times fully observe the Ordinance in collecting, maintaining and using your personal information. We will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.   
|  |  | What kinds of personal information does AFI request from you and how is it used?  
---|---|---  
|  | How do you update or modify your personal information?  
|  | How do you un-subscribe or delete your name from the AFI database?  
|  | Will AFI disclose any of your personal information?  
|  | How secure is your personal information?  
|  | Does AFI.com use cookies?  
|  | Will AFI notify you of any change to the privacy policy?  
To return to the Web site, please use the back button on your browser or click the 'HOME' button.   
What kinds of personal information does AFI request from you and how is it used?   
When subscribing to the AFI service, we ask you for your name, email address, mailing address, phone and fax number. One of the features of the subscription package is that the site can be customized to your requirements. To support this personalization of your subscription package we require that you provide us with the above information about yourself. This information will be protected and used for internal purposes only. We will not knowingly or intentionally release your personal information to any third party without your express consent to do so unless in accordance with this policy.   
We may also collect your credit card information for the purposes of payment of our subscription fee.   
We use your e-mail address and, if necessary, your mailing address or fax number, to keep you up to date with your account and any new features that we may develop on the AFI site.   
As we aim to keep improving the functionalities and the content of the AFI site, we do provide you with the option to provide additional personal information through either the subscription page or direct contact with us. This information may include: Occupation, Interested Markets, Gender, Age /Date of Birth, Education, Income, Trading Experience and Customer Comments. The provision of this information is not mandatory, yet in order for us to provide better service to you, we would appreciate it if you would complete the section relating to such information. Any information submitted here is used for marketing purposes only and will not be disclosed to any third parties except in accordance with this Statement or as required by law. Any personal correspondence we receive from you, either letters or email, will be kept on file, but not disclosed to any third parties except in accordance with this Statement or as required by law. Unless with your express consent or as required by law, we will only use your personal information for the purpose for which it was collected.   
How do you update or modify your personal information?   
You may access, update or modify your personal information at any time by using the 'Change Details' field under 'Tools' on the Web site or by emailing to [support@afi.com](mailto:support@afi.com). To safeguard your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or permitting corrections to your information.   
You may also request a copy of any personal information about you held by us on reasonable notice to us at [katrina@afi.com](mailto:katrina@afi.com).   
How do you un- subscribe or delete your name from the AFI database?   
To terminate your subscription to AFI's services, we require you to notify us at [admin@afi.com](mailto:admin@afi.com) at any time. A confirmation email will be sent to you to confirm your cancellation. The account will be closed within two (2) business days of confirmation. Each subscription term is three (3) months, and the term will be automatically extended for a further three (3) months unless we, or you, give the other written notice (including email) of termination at least five (5) business days prior to the expiration of the current term. AFI may terminate the subscription at any time by notice to you.   
After termination of your subscription, we will take all practical steps to ensure that your information will promptly be deleted. We will retain information on subscribers for a period of 7 years, in order to satisfy our reporting requirements for taxation purposes.   
Will AFI.com disclose any of your personal information?   
AFI.com is a subscription-based site. It is not dependent on support from advertisers. We will not sell, trade or rent personal information about our clients to anyone. However, we may share selected information with third party service providers who provide services to us in connection with the operation of our business and transfer such information outside Hong Kong in accordance with the Ordinance if necessary and with your consent. Other than that, we will not release or disclose your information unless such release or disclosure is, required by any applicable law. We will closely guard your anonymity - information we collect about you will not be disclosed by us to any other party in a form that would identify you.   
AFI.com uses industry-leading technology to secure your personal information. Only authorized AFI employees who are bound by confidentiality agreements with us have access to data provided by clients. We have security functions in place to ensure that your information is secure from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. We will try our best to ensure that our product partners adhere to the same standard.   
How secure is your personal information?   
We have several layers of technology to ensure the confidentiality of your transactions.   
|  |  |  \- 40-bit SSL v3.   
---|---|---  
|  |  AFI.com uses the industry standard SSL Version 3 (Secure Sockets Layer) protocol, to encrypt and secure your data between your browser and our SUN servers.   
|  |  Browser Encryption.   
|  |  It is important that you use a secure browser. Netscape Navigator, Netscape Communicator and Microsoft Internet Browser are all recognized as secure browsers.   
|  |  Username, Password and Secure ID's.   
|  |  To access account information, your portfolio or your subscription information (secure areas), you must provide a User Name and a Password. To change your password go to here.   
|  |  Firewalls and Physical Security   
|  |  Multiple Firewalls are used to ensure that AFI.com's systems are shielded from any unauthorized Internet traffic. The purpose of a Firewall is to make sure that only AFI.com traffic is allowed to pass to our network and systems: All other traffic is rejected. Firewalls also create logs of network traffic that allow for centralized auditing and security monitoring. Once information has been entered, AFI.com uses an encrypted network to transport data between all our systems and our partners to ensure your information is protected. Security is an on-going process: we have round the clock monitoring of the systems and network, and will conduct regular reviews of our security systems by professionals.   
|  |  Company Access Rights   
|  |  Each authorized user, including each AFI.com employee, only has access to very specific data. These users have very specific and defined roles, with access rights which are limited accordingly.   
|  |  Independent Review   
|  |  AFI.com is one of the few international sites to self impose quarterly 3rd party audits to verify that we are in full compliance with all aspects of our privacy policy. In addition AFI.com keeps detailed access logs for clear audit purposes.   
Does AFI.com use cookies?   
A cookie marks and identifies visitors to an Internet site. The use of cookies is an industry standard - you'll find them at most major Web sites. AFI.com uses cookies at Login registration and in places such as portfolio management tools, to allow subscribers to customize information and have it available for subsequent visits.   
Cookies can make your use of online services easier and more personalized. Cookies are placed on your browser by AFI.com and can only be read and understood by AFI.com. Please note that a cookie does not read your hard drive, nor is it intelligible or accessible by any other site.   
If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser to alert you of a cookie being offered, or reject all cookies. Go to the "help" section of your browser for instructions. If cookies are blocked a failure to log in will occur and access to subscription information will be denied.   
Contact AFI:   
We appreciate your business and welcome any comments or feedback in regard to AFI.com's services. If you have a question, comment, problem or concern regarding AFI.com's privacy policy, you can contact us at: [admin@afi.com](mailto:admin@afi.com).
